Ildebrando Quinchoa

Web Developer

Independent junior web developer knowledgeable with front end and back end with Django, capable of building responsive web pages (mock up to code or not) and setting up web applications with Django and well understanding on the MVC pattern. Experienced in the design of relational databases and Hands on with CSS optimization using Sass.

- Venezuela
- https://ildebr.github.io/portfolio/
- ildebrandoefrain@gmail.com
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/ildebran do-quinchoa-5a6343219
- nttps://github.com/ildebr

SKILLS

React Django Basic Proficient HTML 5 CSS3 Advanced Advanced Javascript jQuery Competent Competent Sass **Database** Proficient Proficient

Rest API SQL
Competent Competent

Illustrator Photoshop
Competent Competent

Laravel Basic

LANGUAGES

Spanish English
Native B2

French C2

EDUCATION

UNEG

Informatic Engineering

FUNDAUC

English

WORK EXPERIENCE

Azordev

Front-End Developer

(December 2021 - January 2022)

-Worked with React, Typescript, CSS, GIT to fix bugs on the front-end of websites.

Conjunto Residencial Alta Vista Torre A

(July 2020 - December 2020)

Django Developer

Django application for management of the accounting work of the administrative group in charge of preserving the residential building infraestructure. The application made use of a database of every tennant as well of the residents with magnetic keys of the building on top of keeping records of the building's management spending.

PROJECTS

Pokeapi

https://adoring-allen-c97350.netlify.app

(December 2021 - January 2020)

React application built using data fetched from the API Pokeapi. In this project I used React Hooks, built my own custom hook and the react-router-dom library. All the design and css was done by me.

Notas

http://ilddd.pythonanywhere.com

(August 2021 - August 2021)

Notas is a notetaking django project. -Designed the page. -Wrote the code using Visual Studio 1.56.2 -Implemented MVC pattern. -Implemented registration of users. -Implemented particular views for logged users like 'my notes' and 'edit' views.

Junji Ito's landing page

https://ildebr.github.io/JunjiIto/

A small landing page about the mangaka Junji Ito intended to show abilities with html, css (Sass) and javascript (jQuery). -Designed the page. - Wrote the code using Visual Studio 1.56.2 -Implemented movement through arrows and anchor links with smooth movement using jQuery to manipulate the elements according to user interaction.

Codewell practice

https://ildebr.github.io/codewellprojects/

(September 2021 - September 2021)

Codewell provides assets and designs that can be used to practice html, css and javascript with the main goal of remaking the designs with the provided assets. In this site I show the codewell's project I've finished.

Zaha Hadid

https://ildebr.github.io/ZahaHadid/

(January 2022 - January 2022)

Landing page about the famos architect Zaha Hadid, This is a responsive website made with html, css and the typed.js library for the animation of the text.